export const quiz = {
    totalQuestions: 10,
    questions: [
      {
        id: 1,
        question: '01',
        answers: ['1', '2', '3', '4'],
        correctAnswer: '1',
      },
      {
        id: 2,
        question: '02',
        answers: ['1', '2', '3', '4'],
        correctAnswer: '2',
      },
      {
        id: 3,
        question: '03',
        answers: ['1', '2', '3', '4'],
        correctAnswer: '3',
      },
      {
        id: 4,
        question: '04',
        answers: ['1', '2', '3', '4'],
        correctAnswer: '4',
      },
      {
        id: 5,
        question: '05',
        answers: ['1', '2', '3', '4'],
        correctAnswer: '1',
      },
      {
        id: 6,
        question: '06',
        answers: ['1', '2', '3', '4'],
        correctAnswer: '2',
      },
      {
        id: 7,
        question: '07',
        answers: ['1', '2', '3', '4'],
        correctAnswer: '3',
      },
      {
        id: 8,
        question: '08',
        answers: ['1', '2', '3', '4'],
        correctAnswer: '4',
      },
      {
        id: 9,
        question: '09',
        answers: ['1', '2', '3', '4'],
        correctAnswer: '1',
      },
      {
        id: 10,
        question: '10',
        answers: ['1', '2', '3', '4'],
        correctAnswer: '2',
      },
    ],
  };